pandagossips.com 2019-05-07

# Privacy Policy

Panda Gossips has provided this Privacy Policy to describe our practices with regard to the Personal Information (as defined below) we collect from our users of our website, http://pandagossips.com (the “Website”) and our online services (the “Services”). 

Please note, if you are a non U.S. user of our Website or Services, by visiting our Website and/or providing us with any kind of information, you acknowledge and accept that your Personal Information may be processed for the purposes identified in the Privacy Policy. Additionally, your Personal Information may be obtained and processed in the country and/or other countries, including the United States, where laws regarding processing of Personal Information may be less strict in comparison to the laws in your country. Sharing your information with Panda Gossips means that you are agreeing to such transfer. 

For clarification, the phrase “Personal Information” in this Privacy Policy refers to the information that allows one to identify or contact you. For example, your name, address, telephone number, e-mail address, to name a few. In other words, any non-public information about you that is related to any of the foregoing information. In terms of “Anonymous Information” in this Privacy Policy, we mean any information that is not associated or linked to your Personal Information. Anonymous Information does not enable identification of or contact with individual persons.

A note in relation to children. Panda Gossips’ Website and Services are not directed to children in any means. Children are not suitable to use our Website as well as Services. We do not create content for our Website and Services that are designed to attract people under the age of 13. Protecting the privacy of children is important to Panda Gossips. Thus, we reject any Personal Information from people we are able to identify who are under 13 years of age. Any users who are under 13 years of age will be removed immediately. Meaning, that user’s Personal Information will be permanently removed from our databases to prevent them from using our Site and Services. 

## What Information Does Panda Gossips Collect?

## Personal Information 

Generally, the Personal Information we gather at Panda Gossips enables us to provide our Services to our users and helps us understand how our Site and/or Services are being used. We collect Personal Information that has been submitted to us voluntarily by our users in the course of their use of the Site and/or Services. Users that communicate with Panda Gossips via email, your information that is contained within your communications to us will be collected and stored in our databases. Please note, any information you choose to share with us reflects how much you want other users to know about you. You are entitled to not provide us with certain information about you, but this may limit the features of the Site and/or Services you are able to use. 

Panda Gossips may also require users to create an “Account” in order to have access to particular features on the Website. You may register with Panda Gossips via a third party social networking website (“SNS”), for example Facebook, using your Account and log-in credentials. By clicking on social media links on our website, you will be directed to enter your SNS credentials for the SNS. By doing so, you are giving permission to us, our Website and Services access to your Personal Information. Additionally, you are granting the third party or other SNS’s Terms of Use in your use of our Services. Panda Gossips do receive information from your Facebook or other SNS accounts in order to make it easier for you to create an Account with us. Please note, the information we collect will depend on the privacy settings you have with Facebook or other SNS accounts. We encourage you to consult the SNS’s privacy and data practices for more information. You do have the option to disable Facebook Connect at any time by logging into your Account or revising the appropriate settings from within your account settings on the applicable SNS accounts.

If you wish to provide us with comments regarding the content on our Website, we may use a third party service provider (including an SNS) to provide our users with that functionality. If you provide any Personal Information, this will be collected by our third party service provider and not us. Although, it may appear on our Website. We recommend all our users to review the privacy policy of our service providers prior to providing any Personal Information.

When any of our users contribute to Panda Gossips, whether that’d be our Website, Services or both, please be aware that other users will be able to see it. This also includes anonymous visitors to our Website. Therefore, we strongly urge our users to take this into consideration prior to sharing any Personal Information.

## Anonymous Information

Panda Gossips collect the following types of Anonymous Information:

  1. 1\. Information collected by our servers – Panda Gossips’ servers (note, it may be hosted via a third party service provider) are responsible for collecting information from our users. This may include users’ browser type, operating system, Internet Protocol (“IP”) address, to name a few. 
  2. 2\. Log files – Panda Gossips does gather particular information automatically and store it in our log files. This information includes IP addresses, browser type, Internet service provider (“ISP”), referring or exit pages, operating system, date or time stamp, and clickstream data. This information is used to analyze trends, administer our Website, track our users’ movements around the Website, obtain demographic information about our user base, and better tailor our Website and Services to all of our users’ needs and wants. Please note as specified in this Privacy Policy, we do not link this automatically-collected date to Personal Information.
  3. 3\. Cookies – They are known as small pieces of information that a website sends to your computer’s hard drive while you are viewing the website. Panda Gossips may use both session Cookies (which expire once the browser is closed) and persistent Cookies (stays on your computer until you delete them) to provide our users with a more personal and interactive experience on our Website. It helps make Panda Gossips more useful to our users and tailors the experience to meet our users’ interests, needs and wants. If you do not wish to accept Cookies from our Services, then please instruct your browser, by changing its settings, to stop accepting Cookies or to prompt you before accepting a Cookie from the websites you wish to visit. For more information, please contact your browser’s technical information. Given that you do not wish to accept Cookies, unfortunately, you may not be able to use all portions of the Service or all functionality of the Service. 
  4. 4\. Collection of information by Advertisers – Panda Gossips may use third parties to serve advertisements on the Website. Certain third parties may automatically collect information about your visits to his and other websites, your IP address, your ISP, the browser you use to visit our Website (but not your name, address, e-mail address or telephone number). Information collected may be used, among other things, to deliver advertisements targeted to your specific interest. Additionally, to better understand the usage and visitation of our Website and the other sites tracked by these third parties. This policy does not apply to, and Panda Gossips is not responsible for, Cookies or pixel tags in third party advertisements. We encourage all our users to check the privacy policies of advertisers and/or ad services to learn more about their use of Cookies and possibly other technologies. 
  5. 5\. Disclosure – We may use Google Analytics and other third party services to help analyze how our users use our Website and for other business purposes. Such third party services use Cookies to collect information. This may include how often users visit the Website, what pages they visit, and what other sites they used prior to coming to our Website. We obtain this particular kind of information to help improve Panda Gossips’ Website and Services. Please note, we do not combine the information generated through the use of Google Analytics with your Personal Information. However, please be aware that Google Analytics plants a persistent Cookie on your browser to identify you as a unique user the next time you visit our Website. This Cookie cannot be used by anyone else, but Google. Google’s ability to use and share information collected by Google Analytics about your visits to our Website is restricted by their Terms of Use and Privacy Policy. 

## How Does Panda Gossips Use The Collected Information?

## Personal Information

  1. 1\. We aim to provide our users with Services, which include personalizing the Services for you
  2. 2\. Market our Services to our users that we believe may be of interest to them
  3. 3\. Respond to our users’ requests, resolve disputes and/or troubleshoot problems
  4. 4\. Improve the quality of our Website and Services 
  5. 5\. Communicate with our users about our Website and Services

Panda Gossips may use Personal information to create Anonymous Information records by excluding information that makes the information personally identifiable to a specific individual. 

## Anonymous Information 

We may use Cookies to keep track of logins and personalize users’ experience. Anonymous Information may be used for business purposes, for example, to enhance our Website and/ or Services. We may also use Anonymous Information to contact users, notify users of new content, and/or market our Services to our users on our Website or through our Services. 

## How Does Panda Gossips Disclose Its Information?

## Personal Information

  1. 1\. To third party vendors who help us provide the Services or the Site
  2. 2\. To third parties to whom users ask Panda Gossips to send Personal Information 
  3. 3\. To a parent company, any subsidiaries, joint ventures, or other companies under a common control (collectively, “Affiliates”). Note, we will require our Affiliates to honour this Privacy Policy
  4. 4\. In connection with or during negotiation of any merger, financing, acquisition or dissolution, transaction or proceeding involving sale, transfer, divestiture, or disclosure of all or a portion of our business or assets. In the event of an insolvency, bankruptcy, or receivership, Personal Information may also be transferred as a business asset. If another company acquires our company, business, or assets, that company will possess the Personal Information collected by us and will assume the rights and obligations regarding your Personal Information as described in this Privacy Policy
  5. 5\. If we believe in good faith that such disclosure is necessary to (a) resolve disputes, investigate problems, or enforce our Terms and Conditions; (b) comply with relevant laws or to respond to requests from law enforcement or other government officials relating to investigations or alleged illegal activity, in which case we can (and you authorize us to) disclose Personal Information without subpoenas or warrants served on us; or (c) protect and defend our rights or property or the rights and property of you or third parties.

When users submit information to Panda Gossips for public areas of our Services, we may make it publicly available on our Website via our Services or on other media and services for our business purposes.

Some of our Services may enable users to post content to SNSs, for example, Facebook. If users choose to do this, we will provide information to such SNSs in accordance with our users’ elections. By doing so, users acknowledge and agree that they are solely responsible for their use of those websites and that it is their responsibility to review the terms of use and privacy policy of the third party provider of such SNSs. Panda Gossips will not be responsible or liable for: (i) the availability or accuracy of such SNSs; (ii) the content, products or services on or availability of such SNSs; or (iii) users’ use of any such SNSs.

## Anonymous Information

Panda Gossips reserve the right to disclose Anonymous Information publicly without restriction. 

## How Does Panda Gossips Control Its Users’ Information?

Users may be able to review and/or change particular aspects of their Personal Information by logging into the Website and accessing their Account. By doing so, you authorize Panda Gossips to use and disclose any new or modified information that you provide in accordance with this Privacy Policy, and you agree that we are under no obligation to delete or modify information that you have previously chosen to provide us. Please note, however, that if we receive information from an SNS, you may not be able to change this information through our Site. You must change this information via the SNS. Panda Gossips will correct any inaccuracies in any Personal Information that we have in our databases once notified of the requested change. We will do our best to process these requested changes as soon as is possible, but it may take up to thirty (30) days to make requested changes.

Upon your request, we will close your Account. We may retain your Personal Information to comply with laws, prevent fraud, resolve disputes, troubleshoot problems, assist with any investigations, enforce our Terms and Conditions, and take other actions otherwise permitted by law.

## Does Panda Gossips Disclose Its Information To Third Parties?

Panda Gossips’ Privacy Policy addresses only our use and disclosure of information we collect from and/or about the users on our Website and Services. Please take into careful consideration, if users wish to disclose information to others, or authorize us to do the same under this Privacy Policy, the use and disclosure restrictions contained in this Privacy Policy will not apply to any third party. We do not control the privacy policies of third parties, and you are subject to the privacy policies of those third parties where applicable.

Our Website may contain content or links to other websites that are not owned or controlled by us. We have no control over, do not review and are not responsible for the privacy policies of or content displayed on such other websites. If our users click on such a link, they will leave our Website and go to another. During this process, another entity may collect Personal Information or Anonymous Information from you. The Site may also contain links to other websites controlled by us but which operates under different privacy policies. Panda Gossips strongly encourage its users to review the privacy policy of any new websites they wish to visit. 

## Does Panda Gossips Change Its Privacy Policy? 

Yes, we do. This Privacy Policy may be updated from time to time for any reason. Panda Gossips will notify its users of any changes to our Privacy Policy by posting the new Privacy Policy here (https://pandagossip.com/privacy). Panda Gossips recommends all its users to refer to this Privacy Policy regularly for any changes.
